We have re -established three regiments and an aircraft fleet.
K 4 in Arvidsjaur.
AMF 4 in Gothenburg.
In 13 in Falun.
And F 16 in Uppsala.
The bandages will contribute to a more sustainable organization -
- Where we will continue to train more conscripts.
And we get a clear geographical presence in strategically important areas.
We have received new equipment but also renewed existing.
Among other things, we have received the Robot System Patriot-
- A brand new ability that meets the threat development in our immediate area.
Our efforts in Mali are difficult and demanding, but of great importance to Africa and Europe.
The effort for several years in Afghanistan has also made a difference.
Our part in the evacuation from Afghanistan was an operation of the ultimate class.
The Armed Forces play a central role in total defense development.
How the total defense is to be developed has been made clear in action:
The document that ÖB and DG MSB have agreed.
We must never lose focus on our culture.
How we are against each other, and with each other, is important for our ability.
With clarifications on the development of the total defense and our central role -
- In 2021 we have shown samples of foresight.
So that Sweden is better equipped for tomorrow's threat.